Alice: I think, for the majority of people, that is the case,
but I also think we can’t deny the fact that families come in all shapes and sizes.
James: And as I’ve got older, and had, you know, kids and a family,
that’s kind of taken centre stage.
Debbie: When I was younger, friends were really important, once my children came along,
that was my main focus.
Debbie: Everything that I had was invested in them,
so therefore my family unit became the most important thing.
Debbie: I have now discovered that as much as my family have been there for me,…
Debbie: …my two sons have been my rocks, and they really have been amazing,…
Debbie: …my friends are the ones that have got me through everything,
because they are of the same age as me, the same generation.